(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T00:13:00.863373",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
#OmaruPolkaBirthdayFestival2026
新曲のお披露目あり！ 「Glitter Love」
Featuring a new song reveal: "Glitter Love"!
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名
Polka's concert guest list: A record-breaking 10 Hololive members!
遥か天空響いている 祈りは奇跡に
Echoing in the distant skies, prayers become miracles.
ETERNAL BLAZE
[Song: ETERNAL BLAZE]
真夜中の蒼に溶けて 流れてく涙の粒
My flowing teardrops dissolve into the blue midnight.
迷いなく包み込む 温もりに出会った
Without hesitation, I found a warmth that envelops me.
真っ白な雪のように どこまでも素直な言葉
Everyday words as honest and pure as white snow,
鉄の羽根纏った 僕を動かしてく
set me in motion, freeing me from my steel wings.
傷つくたびに 優しくなれる
Each time I get hurt, I can become kinder.
君のその笑顔だけ 守り抜きたい
I want to protect only your smile to the very end.
願いはひとつ
That is my single wish.
時を越え刻まれた 悲しみの記憶
Transcending time is a carved memory of sorrow.
まっすぐに受け止める 君は光の戦士
Facing it head-on, you are a warrior of light.
あの日の胸に灯った 永遠の炎
The eternal flame lit in my heart that day,
深い闇 解き放って
released me from the deep darkness,
自由のトビラ 開いてく
opening the door to freedom.
強く果てない 未来へ
Into the strong and endless future.
冷たい緑の月に 映し出すココロの影
The cool green moon projects the shadow of my heart.
寂しげに呟いた 「君のそばにいたい」
Lonesomely murmuring, "I want to be by your side."
真実と向き合うこと 教えてくれた勇気は
The courage you gave me to face the truth
僕を駆け巡って 夢に目覚めてゆく
courses through me as I awaken to my dreams.
触れ合う気持ち 離れないように
Never wanting our touching feelings to part,
しっかりと抱きしめて
hold me tightly.
確かな想い 貫いてゆく
This certain feeling will penetrate through.
銀の海に隠した 空白のページ
A blank page hidden in the silver sea.
君だけが知っている 「本当」を僕に見せて
Show me the "truth" that only you know.
吹き荒れる切なさに 生まれゆく誓い
A vow born amidst the raging sorrow.
もう何も怖くはないよ
I am no longer afraid of anything.
結んだ視線 そらさずに
Without turning away my fixed gaze,
大切な「今」始める
we will begin our precious "now".
君が君でいられる場所
The place where you can be yourself,
幻にさらわれぬように
so that you won't be swept away by illusions.
消えない雨の苦しみも
Even the pain of the never-ending rain,
鍵を壊して ぶつけてよ
break the lock and release it.
隣にいるから 全てを信じて
Because I am by your side, believe in everything.
時を越え刻まれた 悲しみの記憶
Transcending time is a carved memory of sorrow.
まっすぐに受け止める 君は光の戦士
Facing it head-on, you are a warrior of light.
あの日の胸に灯った 永遠の炎
The eternal flame lit in my heart that day,
深い闇
the deep darkness...
解き放って
Release me...
自由の扉 開いてく
...and open freedom's door.
強く
I boldly step...
果てない未来へ
...into the endless future.
そう、きっとここから
Yes, it starts right here...
始まる...
...it begins.
お待たせ、みんな！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
今年もポルカの誕生日が始まったよ！
Polka's birthday has begun this year as well!
タイトルは、あ、かっこいい、グリッターラブ！
The title is, ah, the cool "Glitter Love"!
というわけで、ハッシュタグはこちら！
So, the hashtag is this!
尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026で、いっぱい、いっぱい呟いてね！
Please tweet lots and lots with #OmaruPolkaBirthday2026!
はい！
Yes!
いや、今回のテーマがまず、愛と勇気と戦う女の子になってます！
Well, first of all, this time's theme is a girl fighting with love and courage!
そして、見てくださいこのステージ！
And please look at this stage!
い、はー！ すごい広い！
Whoa! It's so spacious!
おー！ なんとですね、広いんですけど、まずスクリーンが超巨大大迫力！
And although it's spacious, first of all, the screen has super massive impact!
なんとなんといつもの3倍くらい頑張りました、いや、頑張ってもらいました！
And we worked about three times harder than usual—well, they worked hard for me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
というわけでですね、ここからゲストの方々がたくさんいらっしゃいます！
So, from here on, we have many guests!
もう、ホロメンだけなら多分尾丸ポルカ史上最多のゲスト数だと思っております！
If we're talking about Holo-members, I think this is probably the largest guest list in Omaru Polka history!
それをね、これからノンストップでお送りするので楽しんで行ってください！
We'll be bringing them to you non-stop, so please enjoy!
というわけで、いくぞー！
So, here we go!
遺伝子レベルの
At a genetic level,
インディペンダント
Independent,
絶望も希望も
despair and hope together,
抱いて
embrace them,
足掻け 命尽きるまで
and struggle until your life meets its end.
光と飛沫のkiss
A kiss of light and spray,
恋のような
like love,
虹のバースデイ
marks a rainbow birthday.
どんな美しき日も
No matter how beautiful the day,
何かが生まれ
when something is born,
何かが死ぬ
something else dies.
せめて唄おう
At least let us sing,
I love you
世界が酷い地獄だとしても
even if the world is a cruel hell.
せめて伝えよう
At least let us convey,
I love you
解放の時は来た
The time for liberation has come.
星降る
The stars fall,
天へと
to the heavens.
響き飛べ！リバティ ソング
Ring out! Our liberty song!
Stardust!!
そして奇跡は待つモノじゃなくて
And miracles aren't things you wait for,
その手で創るものと…吼えろ！
but things you make with your own hands... Howl!
涙した過去の苦痛を
Turn the tearful pain of the past
レクイエムにして
into a requiem.
生ある全のチカラで
With all the power of the living,
輝け future world
shine, future world!
信じ照らせ
Believe and illuminate!
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Celestial Stars, Galaxy Cross!
一人じゃないことを
That you are not alone,
やがて君は
soon you will
知る日の為
come to know.
指先伝うハートスロブ
A heartthrob passing through fingertips,
分かち合って
sharing it,
明日へと向かう
as we head for tomorrow.
永遠なる空に
Amidst this boundless sky,
I feel you
自由の魂は殺せはしない
A spirit so free could never die.
不滅なる夢に
Even in this eternal dream,
I feel you
大志へと拳を握れ
Be ambitious, take up your sword,
運命も
and sever fate
終極も
and finality
断ち切る チカラで
with your power!
そして重ねた勇...
And the gathered courage...
煌めき 煌めき 煌めき
Sparkling, sparkling, sparkling...
十字となって 闇を暴く
...becoming a cross to expose the darkness!
駆け抜けたあの丘には
On that hill we ran through,
神様も知らない
unknown even to God,
歴史なき光 誇る
we boast a light with no history.
My faith and brave heart
この絆
This bond is...
星天ギャラクシィクロス
...the Seiten Galaxy Cross!
逆光の翼で
With wings of backlight,
Just trust dream
just trust the dream!
焦がれる炎で
With yearning flames,
Deep mission
a deep mission!
覚悟背負い 戦おう
Let's shoulder our resolve and fight!
そして奇跡は 待つものじゃなくて
And roar that miracles aren't to be awaited,
その手で創るものと 吠えろ
but created by your own hands!
何度だって何度だって 立ち上がろうか
No matter how many times, let us stand up again and again
生命ある全の力で
with all the strength of our living souls!
輝けFuture world
Shine, future world!
信じ照らせ
Believe and light it up,
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
Let's sing! Let's spin!
Let's dance! Let's spurt!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
プリキュア！
Precure!
Let's sing! Let's spin!
Let's dance! Let's spurt!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
ときめき 出逢い 変わってく世界
Excitement, encounters, and a changing world...
未来
...the future!
1+1+1= 無限
1 + 1 + 1 = Infinity!
唇からこぼれる歌は
The song spilling from our lips...
ららららりらら
Lalalala rilara...
プリズム 眩しい光
...is a prism of dazzling light.
3人寄れば 最高の
When the three of us gather, the best...
始まるタペストリー (Don't worry enjoy together)
...tapestry begins! (Don't worry, enjoy together!)
ハミング
Humming!
ジャズロック
Jazz rock!
カンツォーネ (ステップ) ゴー・ダンス・ポーズ
Canzone (Step) Go! Dance! Pose!
輝く日々でいいよね
A sparkling daily life is great, isn't it?
好きな 好きな
Our favorite, favorite...
フレーズを
...phrases...
シンフォニー！
...form a symphony!
夢を乗せて 君やあなたのもとへ (for you)
Carrying our dreams to you and everyone! (For you)
もっともっと 輝き合えるね
We can shine together even more and more!
みんな (ラヴ・ラヴ) 一雫ずつクリーンに
Everyone, (Love, love) cleaning up one droplet at a time,
いつだって 笑顔写し合おう (Promise)
let's always reflect each other's smiles! (Promise)
君がいるからパワー 生まれるよ今日も
Because you are here, power is born again today.
咲かせ トリプル ドリーム
Let our triple dreams bloom!
Let's sing! Let's spin!
Let's dance! Let's spurt!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
Let's sing! Let's spin!
Let's dance! Let's spurt!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
一緒だから感じハッピー
Because we're together, we feel happy!
1×1×1= 無限
1 x 1 x 1 = Infinity!
出し惜しみはなしで全部 あげたい
Without holding back, we want to give you everything!
ららららりらら
Lalalala rilara...
ハプニングさえもチョイス (ワン・ツー)
Choosing even the mishaps as our choice! (One, two)
3人寄れば門も吉兆 (ジーニアス)
Three of us together bring good luck at the gate! (Genius)
見せるよきっと伝説のライブ (アンコール頂戴)
We'll definitely show you a legendary live! (Give us an encore!)
ルミエール
Lumière!
ポップコーン
Popcorn!
シャンソン (ブレス) オール・ウェルカム
Chanson (Breath) All welcome!
カテゴリーなどいらないよね
We don't need categories, do we?
好きだ 好きだ
I love it, love it,
思い切り
...with all my heart!
シャッフル！
Shuffle!
羽広げ ハートの奥の奥へ (for you)
Spreading our wings deep, deep into your heart (For you)
気持ちは 輝きでできているの
Our feelings are made of starlight!
一雫ずつクリーンをはみ出しちゃう
Overflowing with purity, one droplet at a time,
嬉しいや楽しい (パレット)
happy and fun! (Palette)
君を知って知らない自分に会えたよ
Knowing you let me meet a version of myself I never knew!
咲かせ トリプル ドリーム
Let our triple dreams bloom!
Let's sing! Let's spin!
Let's dance! Let's spurt!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
君も一緒に！
You too, let's join in!
Let's sing! Let's spin!
Let's dance! Let's spurt!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
輝く日々でいいよね
A sparkling daily life is great, isn't it?
好きな 好きな
Our favorite, favorite...
フレーズを
...phrases...
シンフォニー！
...form a symphony!
夢を乗せて 君やあなたのもとへ (for you)
Carrying our dreams to you and everyone! (For you)
もっともっと 輝き合えるね
We can shine together even more and more!
みんな
Everyone!
やったー！
Yay!
瞳の奥に いつまでも笑顔を写し合おう
Let's keep reflecting our smiles in each other's eyes forever.
キミがいるから パワー生まれるよ 今日も
Because you are here, power is born within me today too!
Try, Try, Trio Dreams!
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance! Let's bound!
Let's smile! Let's fly! Woo, peace!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
暗闇のまん中 まっすぐな眼差し
In the middle of the darkness, with a straight gaze...
立ち上がる姿 ちゃんと見ていたよ
...I was watching you stand up properly.
閉じ込められそうな 心を奮い立たせ
Stirring up a heart that feels like it's being locked away...
おさまりきらない 輝きを放ち
...emitting a radiance that cannot be contained.
射抜かれた胸の奥 焼きついた眩しさは
The brightness burned into the depths of my pierced heart...
それだけでもう 理由になる 待っていて
...is already enough of a reason. Please wait for me!
取り戻したい 光の世界
I want to take back the world of light...
その笑顔 勇気 涙 夢 希望の兆し
...that smile, courage, tears, dreams, and signs of hope.
キミと明日を願うチカラで
With the power of wishing for tomorrow with you...
うまれる わたしたちのハーモニー 響け
...our harmony is born. Let it resound!
それでも暗闇は 訪れてしまうもの
Even so, darkness will eventually come.
惑わされないで キミはキミだから
Don't be led astray, because you are you.
渡しあえた日々が ハートを輝かせる
The days we shared make our hearts shine...
ひとりじゃないこと 気づかせてくれる
...reminding us that we are not alone.
抱えきれないほどの「ありがとう」のかわりに
Instead of saying "thank you" too much to contain...
鍵をかけて ひとつになる 受け止めて
...we lock our hands and become one. Embrace it!
取り戻すんだ 光の未来
We will take back the future of light!
今 アツイ オモイ 繋ぐ 声 叶えに行くよ
Now, with passionate feelings and connected voices, let's make it come true!
キミと一緒に 願える奇跡
The miracle of being able to wish together with you...
かさねて 広がっていく ハーモニー
...overlapped and spreading, our harmony expands!
目覚める時が来たね ホントの自分になる
The time has come to awaken and become our true selves...
満ちる運命
...to our fulfilling destiny.
取り戻したい 光の世界
I want to take back the world of light...
その笑顔 勇気 涙 夢 希望の兆し
...that smile, courage, tears, dreams, and signs of hope.
キミと明日を願うチカラで
With the power of wishing for tomorrow with you...
うまれる わたしたちのハーモニー 響け
...our harmony is born. Let it resound!
day by day 日に日に 募るの 乙女心
Day by day, my feelings as a girl keep growing stronger.
同じクラス 斜め前の おとなしい人
A quiet classmate sitting diagonally in front of me...
格好よくはない だけど優しい
He's not really cool, but he's kind,
いつも頼れる彼
a guy I can always rely on.
放課後 恋愛相談の帰り道
On the way back from our after-school love advice session,
何だって話せる 親友の女の子
there's my female best friend whom I can talk to about anything.
スポーツ万能
She's athletic,
勉強もできて
smart,
女子力マックスです
and her femininity is at maximum.
どこにでもある
It's a common story
よくあること
that happens all the time.
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she said...
「あのね、実は私 好きな人がいるの…！」って
"You know, actually, I have someone I like...!"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously?!
三角形 三角形
A triangle, a triangle...
恋は気まぐれ
love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で
In an instant, in an instant,
崩れるバランス
the balance falls into pieces.
ベタな漫画みたいなフラグ
Like a cliché manga flag,
まさかね
there's no way
自分が立てちゃうなんて
I would be the one to trigger it,
残念すぎます！
this is so unfortunate!
三角形 三角形
A triangle, a triangle...
恋は不安定
love is so unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃって
It's not a category
じゃ済まないカテゴリー
where you can just say "just kidding".
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship are swaying,
なんか青春しちゃいます
I'm really feeling the youth,
私 困っちゃいます
but I'm so in trouble.
完敗です！
I completely lose!
お似合いすぎるわ 勝てっこない
You two look too perfect together, I stand no chance.
悔しいけどとか
It's not like I'm frustrated
そんなんじゃなくて本心
or anything, it's my honest feeling.
ていうか既に
Or rather, I'm already
応援モード
in cheerleader mode,
むしろ清々しい
it actually feels refreshing.
だけど彼女は
But she has
不思議な顔
a strange look on her face.
真剣な目で
With serious eyes, she said...
「そうじゃなくて、私 あなたが好き…ごめん」って
"Not him, it's you that I love... sorry."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously?!
三角形 三角形
A triangle, a triangle...
恋は気まぐれ
love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で
In an instant, in an instant,
崩れるバランス
the balance falls into pieces.
私 あなた
Me, you,
彼女と私
her and me.
超絶！複雑！百合展開は
Extremely complicated! A girls' love plot twist
想定外です！
was completely unexpected!
三角形 三角形
A triangle, a triangle...
恋は不安定
love is so unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃって
It's not a category
じゃ済まないカテゴリー
where you can just say "just kidding".
解けないパズル 与えたもうた
You've given me an unsolvable puzzle.
神よ 恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I blame you!
私 悩んじゃいます
Now I'm so worried.
ああ！もう！すごいヤバい！
Ah! Geez! This is so bad!
好きだよ？好きだけど…って、そういう意味じゃなくって！
I like you, okay? I like you, but... not in that way!
だって…女の子同士だし…
I mean... we're both girls...
ねえ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Hey, God, what should we do?
私、どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
ヘルプ・ミー！！！
Help me!!!
なんか変だ～ 愛に国境も
Something is weird... Love knows no borders
歳も性別も関係ない！
or age or gender!
けど、けど、けど！
But, but, but!
三角形 三角形
A triangle, a triangle...
恋は気まぐれ
love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で
In an instant, in an instant,
崩れるバランス
the balance falls into pieces.
普通の恋 夢見てたのに
I was dreaming of a normal love,
ノーマル設定の
but with my default settings,
私じゃちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
this is way too much of a hard game!
三角形 三角形
A triangle, a triangle...
恋は不安定
love is so unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃって
It's not a category
じゃ済まないカテゴリー
where you can just say "just kidding".
彼女のこと 好きになれたら
If only I could fall in love with her,
なんて妄想しちゃいます
I find myself fantasizing like that...
…私 どうかしてます
...I've really gone crazy.
劫々と つづく ショート ショート
An endlessly continuing short-short story...
喪失は 絶対零度 だ
Loss is absolute zero.
今夜は リィンカーネーション
Tonight is reincarnation...
哀しみが
And the sadness...
混沌の 子守唄 歌ってるよ
is singing a lullaby of chaos.
運命に 理由が あるの ならば
If there is a reason for fate...
すべてを 賭けて みたいの
I want to try risking everything...
あなたを 守りたい
I want to protect you.
どこまでも 高く 飛べるわ
We can fly infinitely high!
どこまでも 強く 強く なれるわ
We can become infinitely stronger and stronger!
信じて わたしに 出会えた 奇跡
Believe in the miracle of meeting me!
切り開くは 不死鳥の 炎
What cuts through is the phoenix's flame.
説いて あなたの ドグマ
Explain your dogma.
blackout blackout 眼差しに 泣きたくなるの
blackout blackout / Your gaze makes me want to cry...
flashback flashback 振りほどけ ascend
flashback flashback / Shake it off, ascend...
挑み続けろ
Keep on challenging!
飄々と 佇む ホット・ショット
An aloofly standing hot shot,
わたしが 必要でしょ？
you need me, don't you?
今夜は リィンカーネーション
Tonight is reincarnation...
正しさが
Where righteousness...
ストレイ・シープ 最前線に 押し出すよ
pushes the stray sheep to the front lines.
運命に 理由が あるの ならば
If there is a reason for fate...
優しい 世界を あげたい
I want to give you a gentle world...
あなたを 包むわ
I will embrace you.
どこまでも 速く 射抜くわ
We can pierce through infinitely fast!
どこまでも 熱く 熱く 焦がすわ
We can burn infinitely hot and hot!
信じて わたしに 出会えた 奇跡
Believe in the miracle of meeting me!
切り開くは 不死鳥の 炎
What cuts through is the phoenix's flame.
説いて あなたの ドグマ
Explain your dogma.
blackout blackout 肩越しに 光を見せて
blackout blackout / Show me the light over your shoulder...
flashback flashback 許さない betray
flashback flashback / I won't forgive the betrayal...
進み続けろ 尽きるまで
Keep moving forward until the end!
傍にいると 鼓動が 速くて
When I am by your side, my heart beats so fast...
目眩がする
that I feel dizzy.
全て 捧げる もう 決めたの
I've already decided to offer everything.
最後の チャンス だから もう 離さない
It's the last chance, so I won't let go anymore!
灼に燃ゆる
Burning redly...
未来の風に跨っていけ
ride on the wind of the future!
どこまでも 高く 飛べるわ
We can fly infinitely high!
どこまでも 強く 強く なれるわ
We can become infinitely stronger and stronger!
信じて わたしに 出会えた 奇跡
Believe in the miracle of meeting me!
闇夜も 望めば 赫夜にするから
Because if you wish, I'll turn even the dark night into a glowing one!
切り開くは 不死鳥の 炎
What cuts through is the phoenix's flame.
説いて あなたの ドグマ
Explain your dogma.
blackout blackout 眼差しに 泣きたくなるの
blackout blackout / Your gaze makes me want to cry...
flashback flashback 振りほどけ ascend
flashback flashback / Shake it off, ascend...
挑み続けろ
Keep on challenging!
blackout blackout 肩越しに 光を見せて
blackout blackout / Show me the light over your shoulder...
flashback flashback 許さない betray
flashback flashback / I won't forgive the betrayal...
進み続けろ 尽きるまで
Keep moving forward until the end!
神様に恋をしてた頃は
When I was in love with God...
こんな別れが来るとは思ってなかったよ
I never thought a farewell like this would come.
もう二度と触れられないなら
If I can never touch you again...
せめて最後に
then at least, at the very end...
もう一度抱きしめて欲しかったよ
I wanted you to hold me one more time.
It's long long good-bye
It's a long, long goodbye...
さよなら さよなら 何度だって
Goodbye, goodbye, no matter how many times...
自分に 無情に 言い聞かせて
I mercilessly tell myself.
手を振るのは 優しさだよね?
Waving goodbye is a form of kindness, right?
今強さが欲しい
Right now, I want strength.
貴方に出会い STAR輝いて アタシが生まれて
Meeting you, the star shone, and I was born.
愛すればこそ 愛あればこそ
Because of love, because there is love...
希望のない 奇跡を待って どうなるの?
what will happen if I wait for a hopeless miracle?
涙に滲む 惑星の瞬きは gone...
The twinkling of the stars, blurred by my tears, is gone...
忘れられないよ 貴方の温もりも
I won't forget your warmth...
その優しさも 全て包んでくれた両手も
or your kindness, or your hands that embraced everything.
It's long long good-bye
It's a long, long goodbye...
さよなら さよなら 愛しい人
Goodbye, goodbye, my beloved.
貴方が いたから 歩いてこれた
Because you were here, I was able to walk this far.
ひとりなんかじゃなかったよね?
I wasn't alone, was I?
今答えが欲しい
Right now, I want an answer.
燃える様な流星 捕まえて 火を灯して
Catch a burning meteor and light a fire.
愛していたい 愛されてたい<
I want to love, I want to be loved.
冷えたカラダひとつで 世界は どうなるの?
With only this cold body, what will become of the world?
張り続けてた 虚勢が溶けてく long for...
The bluff I kept putting up is melting away, longing for...
どうしてなの?
Why is this?
涙溢れて 止められない
My tears overflow, and I can't stop them.
貴方に出会い STAR輝いて アタシが生まれて
Meeting you, the star shone, and I was born.
愛すればこそ 愛あればこそ
Because of love, because there is love...
希望のない 奇跡を待って どうなるの?
what will happen if I wait for a hopeless miracle?
涙に滲む 惑星の瞬きは gone...
The twinkling of the stars, blurred by my tears, is gone...
もし生まれ変わって また巡り会えるなら
If I am reborn and we can meet again...
その時もきっと アタシを見つけ出して
make sure to find me then, too.
もう二度と離さないで 捕まえてて
And never let me go again, hold onto me.
ひとりじゃないと
That I am not alone...
囁いてほしい
...I want you to whisper.
planet...
聖なる瞳が 痛みを知ったら
If my saint-like eyes learn of pain,
振り向いてごらん
look back...
情熱放つTrick
...at this passion-releasing trick.
崩れる足元
Our crumbling footing,
二人は戻れない
the two of us can't go back.
差し伸べた手をほどかないで
Don't let go of my outstretched hand.
消えるよまた
They disappear once again,
優しい日々が
those tender days.
思い出を汚すのは許せない
I won't allow our memories to be tainted.
ここは裏切りの楽園
This is a paradise of betrayal...
彷徨う心の果てに
...at the end of a wandering heart.
光を求めて
Searching for the light,
祈る言葉届けあなたに
may my words of prayer reach you.
囚われの羽が
Our imprisoned wings
遥かな空へと向かう
head towards the distant sky.
信じたいよ私達
I want to believe that we...
孤独じゃない
...are not alone.
分かり合う (求め合う)
Understanding each other (seeking each other),
絆の中
within our bond.
離さない (離れない)
I won't let go (I won't leave),
始まるDestiny
our beginning destiny.
新たな願いに
To a new wish,
鎖ほどける時
when the chains are undone.
休ませてくれる深い眠りに
Will you let me rest in a deep sleep?
わずかな希望が
A tiny shred of hope
私を強くする
makes me strong,
ぬくもりに触れてみたいから
because I want to feel your warmth.
甦れば
If it's resurrected,
儚き命
this fleeting life...
繰り返す愛しさが導いた
...will be led by this recurring love.
胸に泡沫の調べ
With a fleeting melody in my heart,
流れる世界の終わり
at the end of this flowing world.
諦めはしない
I won't give up,
今が繋ぐ明日探そう
let's search for the tomorrow that connects us now.
ちぎれ舞う羽は
Our torn, fluttering wings
未来の空にも向かう
head towards the sky of the future as well.
忘れないで私達
Don't forget that we...
ひとつのクリスタル
...are a single crystal.
輝いて (眩しくて)
Shine (so dazzlingly),
割れないのよ
we won't break.
離さない (離れない)
I won't let go (I won't leave),
誓いのDestiny
our promised destiny.
Lost the paradise, ah!
消えるよまた
They disappear once again,
優しい日々が
those tender days.
思い出を汚すのは許せない
I won't allow our memories to be tainted.
ここは裏切りの楽園
This is a paradise of betrayal...
彷徨う心の果てに
...at the end of a wandering heart.
光を求めて
Searching for the light,
祈る言葉届けあなたに
may my words of prayer reach you.
囚われの羽が
Our imprisoned wings
遥かな空へと向かう
head towards the distant sky.
信じたいよ私達
I want to believe that we...
孤独じゃない
...are not alone.
分かり合う (求め合う)
Understanding each other (seeking each other),
絆の中
within our bond.
離さない (離れない)
I won't let go (I won't leave),
始まるDestiny
our beginning destiny.
離さない
Don't let go...
見つめて Paradise Lost
Look at me, Paradise Lost!
Wow wow wow wow...
やっとみんな会えたね
We finally get to meet everyone!
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!
たかたった 全力 走りたい
With pit-a-patting hearts, I want to run with all my might!
芝と 砂と キミの 追い切りメニュー
On turf and dirt, our final workout training menu!
Turn up! 声出せ 叫べ
Turn up! Cry out and shout!
それそれ！ はい！ はい！ はい！
There we go! Yes! Yes! Yes!
たかたった 全力 上がりタイム
With pit-a-patting hearts, it's our top-speed final stretch!
ゆずれない夢の途中
In the middle of an unyielding dream,
始めよう ここから最高ストーリー
let's begin the greatest story from right here!
あこがれの 地へ
To the land of our yearning,
(勇気少し借りて)
(Borrowing just a little courage)
語り合った memory
The memories we shared,
(二度と来ない今を)
(Savoring this moment that will never come again)
もう ドキドキ も トキメキ も
Our hearts are already throbbing and fluttering so much,
抑えられない たまんない
we can't hold it back, it's irresistible!
熱い ハラハラ が止まらない
The thrilling excitement won't stop!
キミと
With you,
走り競いゴール目指し
competing as we run toward the goal!
遥か響け届け music
Echo far and wide, reach out, music!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 想い
These feelings that have lasted forever and ever,
夢がきっと叶うなら
if our dreams will surely come true...
あの日のキミに感じた
Believing in that spark
何かを信じて
I felt from you on that day,
春も夏も秋も冬も超え
passing spring, summer, autumn, and winter,
願い焦がれ走れ
run with yearning and prayers!
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory!
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!
たかたった 全力 はじけたい
With pit-a-patting hearts, I want to burst with all my might!
期待 出会い 決意 絆になった
Expectations, meetings, decisions—they all became bonds!
Hands up! 本気で叫べ
Hands up! Shout with all your heart!
それそれ！ はい！ はい！ はい！
There we go! Yes! Yes! Yes!
たかたった 全力 笑いたい
With pit-a-patting hearts, I want to smile with all my might!
ターフのド真ん中
Right in the very center of the turf!
リアルにここから上昇 story
Our story rising from here is completely real!
かけぬけた 日々
The days we ran through,
(昨日よりも今日を)
(Focusing on today more than yesterday)
語り合った glory
The glory we talked about,
(強くなれる理由)
(The reason we can become stronger)
いま 答えてたい "いきてる" と
Right now, I want to show that I am "alive,"
背中押す声 熱くなる
the voice pushing my back gets so hot!
夢は夢のままおわれない
This dream can't end as just a dream!
キミと
With you,
未来描きゴール目指し
visualizing the future as we aim for the goal!
狙え イドメ ツカメ winning
Take aim, challenge, and grasp that winning moment!
ずーっとずーっとずーっとずーっと 想い
These feelings that have lasted forever and ever,
夢はきっと叶うから
because our dreams will surely come true!
あの日キミが流した
Believing in the tears
涙も信じて
you shed on that day, too,
雨も風も雲も闇も超え
surpassing rain, wind, clouds, and darkness,
願い焦がれ走れ
run with yearning and prayers!
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory!
ゆるぎない覚悟決して
With an unwavering determination,
ひとつふたつ ともにつづる記録
each and every record we write down together...
背中に迫る迷いふりはらえ
Shake off the doubts closing in behind you,
いまの自分おいこすだけ
and just surpass the self you are today!
勝ちたい 勝ちたい 勝ちたい キミと勝ちたい
I want to win, I want to win, I want to win, I want to win with you!
未来描きゴール目指し
Visualizing the future as we aim for the goal!
狙え イドメ ツカメ winning
Take aim, challenge, and grasp that winning moment!
ずーっとずーっとずーっとずーっと 想い
These feelings that have lasted forever and ever,
夢はきっと叶うから
because our dreams will surely come true!
あの日キミが流した
Believing in the tears
涙も信じて
you shed on that day, too,
春も夏も秋も冬も超え
passing spring, summer, autumn, and winter,
雨も風も雲も闇も超え
surpassing rain, wind, clouds, and darkness,
勝利へ
Toward victory!
キミと
With you,
走り競いゴール目指し
competing as we run toward the goal!
遥か響け届け music
Echo far and wide, reach out, music!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 想い
These feelings that have lasted forever and ever,
夢がきっと叶うなら
if our dreams will surely come true...
あの日のキミに感じた
Believing in that spark...
夏も秋も冬も超え 願い焦がれ走れ
Cross over summer, autumn, and winter, run with burning desire
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, to victory!
未来描きゴール目指し 狙い挑め掴め winning
Envisioning the future, aiming for the goal, aiming, challenging, and seizing victory!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い 夢はきっと叶うから
Thoughts I've held on to forever and ever, because dreams will surely come true
あの日のキミが流した 涙も信じて
Believe even in the tears you shed that day
雨も風も雲も闇も超え 願い焦がれ走れ
Cross over the rain, the wind, the clouds, and the darkness, run with burning desire
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, to victory!
don't stop! no, don't stop 'til finish!
It's finally the true end
I'm ready for... my destiny
I'm ready for... STARTING OVER
やっと幕を下ろした 最後の瞬間まで
I was finally able to bring down the curtain, until the very last moment
わたしは精一杯に わたしをやりきった
I did my absolute best, I gave it my all
終演の続きは 誰も知らなくていい
No one needs to know what lies beyond the end of the show
涙を置いて 新しい旅に出よう
Let's leave our tears behind and set off on a new journey
熱狂はあなたを選ぶ 違う結末だっただけ
The wild enthusiasm chooses you, it was just a different ending
同じ愛になれなかった Destiny
A destiny where we couldn't share the same love
これまでのすべてを 差し出すような愛だった
It was a love that seemed to offer up everything we had until now
世界の意味が変わるくらいに 肯定された気がしたんだ
I felt so validated, as if the very meaning of the world had changed
何気なさの中で 気づけた最初の奇跡が
The first miracle that I noticed amidst the casual normalcy...
あなたでよかった わたしでよかった 心から思えたよ
...I'm glad it was you, I'm glad it was me, I truly felt that from the bottom of my heart
ずっと遠い未来も ちゃんと覚えていよう
Let's make sure to remember properly, even in the far distant future
自分の抱きしめかた 明日の願いかた
How to embrace myself, how to wish for tomorrow
あなたがいなくても わたしの片隅で
Even if you are not here, in a corner of my heart...
優しい光 消えたりしないとわかる
...I know that a gentle light will never fade away
今はまだ手を振れるほど 道は別れたばかりで
Right now, we can still wave to each other, our paths having only just diverged
後ろ髪に風を感じながら
Feeling the wind blow through the back of my hair
それまでのすべてが あなたに出会うためだった
Everything leading up to that point was just for the sake of meeting you
どの瞬間もムダじゃないこと 本当の意味で知れたから
Because I learned the true meaning of how not a single moment was wasted
次の曲がり角も 自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next corner with my own true self too
いつかに繋がる 新しい一歩 信じて歩き出そう
Believing in a new step that connects to some someday, let's walk forward
心から誰かを愛せた あの日々は
Those days when I could love someone from the bottom of my heart...
間違いなくわたしの Destiny Ah,
...were without a doubt my destiny, ah
これまでのすべてが 新しい力をくれる
Everything up until now gives me new strength
どの瞬間もムダじゃないなら 何が起きても大丈夫だから
If not a single moment was wasted, then no matter what happens, it'll be okay
次の物語も 自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next story with my own true self too
いつかに繋がる わたしのはじまり 信じて歩き出そう
Believing in my beginning that connects to some someday, let's walk forward
To the day we connect, to my beginning... Believing, I'll start walking forward.
再び幕は上がる
Once again, the curtain rises!
聞いていただいたのは新曲の「STARTING OVER」でした！
What you just heard was my brand new song, "STARTING OVER"!
はい！新年1発目、新曲の初披露というわけで
Yes! To kick off the new year, we had the premiere of my new song...
ぬるっとね、新曲をやってしまったんですが
...which I just casually performed like that.
平成感のある、懐かしみを感じる楽曲を
It has a distinct Heisei-era, nostalgic feel to it...
こちらですね、歌わせていただいたんですけれども
...and I'm so happy I got to sing it for you.
この後、この曲が24時から、あ、ともう数時間か
Right after this, at midnight—well, in just a few hours—
24時からですね、1月30日の24時から配信リリースされます！たくさん聞いてください！
...yes, at midnight on January 30th, it will be released digitally! Please listen to it a lot!
今年もね、たくさんオリジナル曲出していきたいです！
I want to release lots of original songs this year too!
そしてそして、もうMCがね、実は最後なのでね
And also, this is actually my final MC segment of the night,
この配信の後にはメンバー限定の配信もあるので、よろしくお願いします！
so after this stream, we'll have a members-only stream! I hope to see you there!
よし、よし、よし！グッズ紹介！
Alright, alright! Time for the merch reveal!
えー、ここには同期のねぽらぼが大集合ということで
And since we have my Genmates, NePoLaBo, gathered here...
ね・ら・ぼ、集まれー！
Ne, Ra, Bo... gather round!
イェーイ！来たー！
Yay! We're here!
はい、ちゃ、ちゃ、ちゃ、ちゃ。初めて呼びました。どうもー。
Cha-cha-cha-cha! This is the first time we've been invited on. Hello!
え、初だっけ？ / ポルカチャンネル初です！
Wait, is this really the first time? / Yes, first time on Polka's channel!
ポルカ、誕生日おめでとう！ / おめでとう！
Polka, happy birthday! / Happy birthday!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
ここまでが流れでございます。はい。
And that's how the intro goes. Yes.
ずっと待ってたから。 / 待ってたよ。
We've been waiting the whole time. / We were indeed!
グッズを紹介させていただきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to introduce my anniversary merch!
みんなでめくりながら、リアクションなどをおのおの取ってくれると嬉しいです。
I'd love it if you guys could react as we reveal each slide.
合点承知！ / ガヤします！
Roger that! / We'll bring the commentary!
尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念グッズ2026、ラインナップはこちら！ドン！
Here is the lineup for Omaru Polka's Birthday Celebration 2026! Bam!
ドン！ / おおー！
Bam! / Whoa!
というわけで、素晴らしい今回のラインナップが揃っております。
As you can see, we have a wonderful lineup this time.
あれ？ポルカ、なんか持ってない？ / ちょっとあれが...
Wait, Polka... aren't you wearing something different? / Wait, that's...
あれれ？あれ？あれ？
Wait, what? Huh? Oh?
ちょっと、なんか持ってます？
Wait, is she holding something?
持ってますよー！ / 持ってますよね。
No, she is! / She definitely is!
というわけで、まず、1つ1つ紹介していきましょう！
Alright, let's introduce them one by one!
まずは、こちら！はい！
First up is this one! Yes!
ポルカの「はじめての抱き枕カバー」になっております！
It's Polka's "First-Ever Body Pillow Cover"!
おー！すごーい！ / かわいい！
Whoa, amazing! / So cute!
え、ちょっとポルカ、これ、パンツ履いてなくないですか？
Wait, Polka... is she not wearing underwear here?
あれ？丸出しじゃないですか？
Wait, isn't she totally exposed?
え、本当だ！
Wait, you're right!
いや、それ、部屋着だよ！部屋着！部屋着だって！
No, those are loungewear! Loungewear, I tell you!
ねねだって、こういう部屋着だろ？
Nene, you wear loungewear like this too, right?
あ、ねねの？ / 違う、違う、違う...
Ah, mine? / No, no, no...
人のチャンネルだからってやりたい放題チャンネルして！
You're treating your own channel like an absolute free-for-all!
お前、シャツで寝たら、シャツ浮くぞ！
If you sleep in just a shirt, it's gonna ride up!
おいやめなさい！シャツ浮くシャツ浮く！浮かないですよ、シャツは！
Hey, stop that! "Ride up, ride up"... No, it won't ride up!
なるほどね。というわけで、「はじめての抱き枕カバー」出します。
I see. So, here is my "First-Ever Body Pillow Cover".
表は通常衣装、裏は彼シャツになってます！
The front features my default outfit, and the back has the oversized boyfriend shirt!
描いていただきました！ / かわいい！
It was illustrated beautifully! / So cute!
はい、ありがとうね、みんな！
Yes, thank you, everyone!
続きまして、ドン！こちら！
Moving on... Bam! Here it is!
「歴代衣装のポルカ ランダムラバーストラップ」です！
The "Polka Past Outfits Random Rubber Strap"!
かわいい！ / いい！
Cute! / Nice!
これまでの衣装のラバーストラップ、のいみ先生に描いていただきました！
These rubber straps of my past outfits were illustrated by Noimi-sensei!
めっちゃいいじゃん、これ！可愛い！
This is so cool! It's adorable!
どの衣装が出るかお楽しみにです。ありがとうね、みんなリアクション、本当に100点満点です。
Look forward to seeing which one you get. Thanks for the reactions, you guys are getting a perfect score.
はい、続きまして、こちら！
Alright, next up is this!
「どれもこれも宝物！思い出バインダー」！
The "Everything is a Treasure! Memory Binder"!
おー！いい！
Whoa! Nice!
これですね、最近みんなも特典でチェキ風ブロマイドカード出してたりするから
Lately, everyone's been releasing Polaroid-style bromide cards as bonuses,
そういうの入れられたり、あとはホロカも入るサイズになっていますので
so you can store those, and it also fits Holo_Cardz!
ぜひぜひいろんな思い出しまってください！ / しまってください！
So please, store all kinds of memories in it! / Store them away!
はい、そして続きましては、こちら！
Yes, and next we have this!
「ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー」！
The "Polka's Tail Keychain"!
おー！可愛い！
Oh! Cute!
一周して流行ってるからね、ポルカのしっぽ型キーホルダー！
Since these are coming back into style, it's a keychain of Polka's tail!
確かに、確かに！平成レトロ、平成レトロみたいな。
True, true! It has that Heisei retro vibe.
平成レトロみたいな感じで、なっております。
Yes, it has a Heisei retro feel to it.
可愛い！
Cute!
はい、こちらもつけてください！そしてボイスも出ます！ボイスはこちら！
Please attach this too! And we have a voice pack! Here it is!
じゃん！「彼シャツポルカの、ただいまの距離。」
Tada! "Oversized Shirt Polka's Distance From You Now."
おー！キャー！
Ooh! Yay!
はい、ASMRボイスです。はい、えーと、まあ、彼シャツのポルカ、ということでちょっと、なんかタイトルもなんか...
Yes, it's an ASMR voice pack. It's "Oversized Shirt Polka," so the title is kind of...
狙ってるじゃん。
You're totally targeting them.
てぇてぇ、てぇてぇ！
Teeteetee!
なんで今日同期呼んじゃったんだろうっていうの一瞬思った、今、恥ずかしくなってきた。
For a second, I wondered why I invited my genmates today. I'm getting embarrassed now.
うー、うー、うー... / お互い、小学生みたいになってる...
Oooh... / We're all acting like elementary schoolers...
えーと、添い寝ASMRというか、抱き枕カバーとイラストの関係があるボイスになってます！
It's a co-sleeping ASMR, so it ties into the body pillow cover's illustration!
おおー！すごーい！
Whoa! Awesome!
でお待たせしました！フルセット購入特典になっております！こちら！
And thanks for waiting! Here is the full set purchase bonus! Look!
チェキ風ブロマイドカード！数量限定が直筆メッセージ、箔押し複製サインになっております！
A Polaroid-style bromide card! The limited edition has a handwritten message and a foil-stamped signature!
通常が箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りでございます。
The standard edition comes with a foil-stamped signature and printed message.
フルセットぜひぜひ買っていただいた方には、特典ボイスとして
And for those who buy the full set, as a bonus voice pack...
「すやすやポルカの、いちばん近い約束。」
...you get "Sleeping Polka's Closest Promise."
キャー！キャー！
Eeeee!
一緒に
Together...
一緒にね、寝ようね、みたいな感じのなんかちょっとそういったボイスになってて。こっちもASMRになってます。
...with a voice that says, "Let's sleep together." This one is also in ASMR.
おおー！
Oh!
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
恥ずかしいな、みんなとやるの、これ。
This is embarrassing, doing this with everyone.
なんか、エッチな女になってる、なって。
I feel like a naughty woman...
いいじゃない！
Nothing wrong with that!
すいません、新年もね、えーと、皆さん改めて、これからよろしくお願いします。
Sorry. Everyone, happy new year, and we look forward to working with you this year too.
というわけでね、今日はみんなで最後に一緒に歌うために呼んできたということで、
And so, since I invited everyone to sing together at the end today...
準備してきます！
...let's get ready!
いってらっしゃーい！
Have a good one!
脚本は捨てちゃおうか
Shall we throw away the script?
さあしかと焼き付けよ！
Now, burn this into your mind!
アドリブの
With this ad-libbed...
熱いパフォーマンス
...hot performance!
屋根裏を飛び出して
Flying out of the attic,
壮大なステージに響く
echoing across a grand stage,
特別なストーリー
is our special story.
瞼の裏には
Behind closed eyelids,
虹が紡ぐ
a rainbow is spun...
星空のメモリ
...with memories of the starry sky.
等身大の愛を込めて
Packing it with true-to-life love,
想像を超える世界へ
we head to a world beyond imagination.
誰も知らないでしょ
Nobody knows yet, right?
Are you ready?
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future lies ahead!
なんて自由だ！笑っちゃうよね
We're so free! It makes me laugh.
ねえ ホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, let's go further than holograms!
誰だって置いてかないよ
We won't leave anyone behind.
ごらん！歓声が呼んでいる
Look! The cheers are calling for us!
スナップからパッと照らす
Shining instantly with a snap...
人生のスポットライト
...is the spotlight of life!
薔薇色のプレミアムショー
A rose-colored premium show...
ここが特等席よ
...and right here is the best seat in the house!
本日ロマンス日和
Today is a fine day for romance.
(天気次第のエチュード)
(An impromptu play depending on the weather)
まるで絵物語
Just like an illustrated tale.
捕まえてよ
Catch me!
(待って)
(Wait!)
ほら
Look!
(待って)
(Wait!)
予想のできない展開に
In an unpredictable turn of events,
ステージは揺れる
the stage is shaking.
格別のストーリー
An extraordinary story.
耳を澄ましたら
If you listen closely,
月が踊る
the moon is dancing...
雨粒のハーモニー
...to the harmony of raindrops.
浮かぶふわふわな空想
Floating fluffy daydreams.
暴走？底なしの本能！
Running wild? My bottomless instinct!
すべて知りたいでしょ
You want to know everything, right?
Hey guys！叫べ 気分は最高？
Hey guys! Shout out! Are you feeling great?
(最高！)
(Great!)
Come on！もっと叫べ 気分は最高？
Come on! Shout louder! Are you feeling great?
(最高！)
(Great!)
ポルカ 終わるか？
Is Polka ending?
終わらない！
It's not ending!
It's showtime！
It's showtime!
繋いだ手 離さないで なんてね
"Don't let go of my hand..." Just kidding!
どうしたって 重たくなっちゃって 困るわ
No matter what, it'll get too heavy, and I'll be in trouble.
いつの日か エピローグを一緒に綴ろう
Let's write the epilogue together someday.
きっと約束よ
It's a promise.
Life goes on！
Life goes on!
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future lies ahead!
なんて自由だ！笑っちゃうよね
We're so free! It makes me laugh.
ねえ ホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, let's go further than holograms!
夢のような花舞台に感情を馳せたら
If we send our emotions to this dream-like stage...
スナップからパッと照らす
Shining instantly with a snap...
人生のスポットライト
...is the spotlight of life!
薔薇色のプレミアムショー
A rose-colored premium show!
どこへだって添い遂げたい
Wherever it is, I want to go all the way with you.
ここが特等席よ
And right here is the best seat in the house!
あんたにゃ もったいない (フー！)
You don't deserve me! (Woo!)
あたしゃ本当 ナイスバディ バディ バディ
I really have a nice body, body, body!
自分で言うくらい
Even if I have to say so myself,
タダじゃない じゃない
I'm not cheap, am I?
じゃない？ あは～ん！
Am I? Ah-ha~n!
熱けりゃ サマーセブン
If it's hot, it's Summer Seven!
寂しけりゃ エブリバディ バディ バディ
If you're lonely, everybody, body, body!
誰にも わからない
No one knows
恋愛って いつ火がつくのか
when love is going to catch fire.
ダイナマイト
Dynamite!
恋はダイナマイト
Love is dynamite!
どんなに 不景気だって
No matter how bad the economy is,
恋はインフレーション
love is an inflation!
こんなに 優しくされちゃ みだら
Being treated this gently makes me feel wild!
明るい 未来に
In a bright future,
就職希望だわ
I hope to find employment!
Wow wow wow wow
日本の未来は (Wow wow wow wow)
Japan's future is (Wow wow wow wow)
世界がうらやむ (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
the envy of the world (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
恋をしよじゃないか (Wow wow wow wow)
Why don't we fall in love? (Wow wow wow wow)
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
なんだか 物足りない
Somehow, something's missing.
どこに立って 愛しててほしいわ
Wherever I stand, I want you to love me!
自分で 伝えるの
Telling you myself
恥ずかしいじゃない
is embarrassing, isn't it?
じゃない？ うぉー！
Isn't it? Whoa!
理想の 二人なら
If we are the ideal couple,
憧れよ エブリバディ バディ バディ
then admire us, everybody, body, body!
誰しも 気づいてない
Nobody has realized that
恋愛って 夢の落とし穴
love is a dream's trap.
ミステリー
Mystery!
恋はミステリー
Love is a mystery!
どんなに 不自然だって
No matter how unnatural it is,
恋のインサイダー
we are love's insiders!
それでも ロマンティックされちゃわ
Even so, being treated romantically is... ah!
幸せ 来る日も
Happiness, day after day,
キャンセル待ちだわ
is on the waiting list!
Wow wow wow wow
あんたの笑顔は (Wow wow wow wow)
Your smile is (Wow wow wow wow)
世界がうらやむ (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
the envy of the world (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
夢があるじゃないか (Wow wow wow wow)
There's a dream in it, isn't there? (Wow wow wow wow)
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
ふわふわふわふわ！
Fuwa fuwa fuwa fuwa!
あは～ん！
Ah-ha~n!
Love, love, love マシーン
Love, love, love machine!
Love, love, love ステーション
Love, love, love station!
Love, love, love ファクトリー
Love, love, love factory!
Love, love, love is so wonderful
イェーイ！
Yay!
Wow wow wow wow
日本の未来は (Wow wow wow wow)
Japan's future is (Wow wow wow wow)
世界がうらやむ (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
the envy of the world (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
恋をしよじゃないか (Wow wow wow wow)
Why don't we fall in love? (Wow wow wow wow)
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
もっと愛して (Wow wow wow wow)
Love me more! (Wow wow wow wow)
あんたも あたしも (Wow wow wow wow)
Both you and I, (Wow wow wow wow)
みんなも 社長さんも (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
everyone, and the company president too! (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
ラブマシーン
Love Machine
「尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026」
新曲『Glitter Love』お披露目あり！ホロメンゲスト10名！
"Omaru Polka Birthday Festival 2026"
New song "Glitter Love" showcase & 10 Hololive guests!